A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Associates, Harry Rand FA1224
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family: Public Relations, 1915-1978; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1915, 1918, 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller – Bio Material, 1965-1971, 1974, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 332)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1943, 1966, 1969-1971, 1976, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 333)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 334)
  - Rockefeller Family – Bio Material, 1967, 1973-1976 (Box 31, Folder 335)
  - "You've Come a Long Way, Baby" by Julie Baumgold, New York magazine article (Abby Rockefeller), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 336)
  - Harvard Divinity School Article re David Rockefeller, 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 337)
  - National Park Literature (Box 31, Folder 338)
  - Subway Station Improvements, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 339)
  - Possible Westchester County Projects, Nina Jones, 1969-1972 (Box 31, Folder 340)
  - Correspondence with the Cousins, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 341)
  - Correspondence with the Cousins: Mailing Addresses, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 341A)
    Restricted - confidential material.
  - "David" by William Hoffman, Published by Lyle Stuart, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 342)
  - Miscellaneous Rockefeller Family (Box 31, Folder 343)
- Research Material, 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Adirondack Park (Box 32, Folder 344)
  - Bronx Zoo (The New York Zoological Society) (Box 32, Folder 345-347)
    Folder 347 - Bronx Zoo: Transportation
  - Columbia, Maryland (Box 33, Folder 348)
  - Energy (Box 33, Folder 349-350)
    Folder 349 - Energy: Special Reports; Folder 350 - Energy: Speeches
  - Environmental Quality (Box 33, Folder 351)
  - Federal Power Commission (Box 33, Folder 352)
  - New Communities (Box 34, Folder 353)
  - Nuclear Power (Box 34, Folder 354)
  - Solid Waste (Box 34, Folder 355)
  - Utility Glossary/Q&A/Directories/Federal Power Commission/State Utility Commissions (Box 34, Folder 356)
  - Winrock Farms (Box 34, Folder 357)